RG 097, Connecticut Commission on the Arts
Connecticut State Library
- Series 5. Artists-in-Schools (A. I. S.) Program
  - A.I.S. by Art Form (Box 30)
    - Poetry and Writing (Box 30)
      - Chase Twichell (Box 30)
      - Robert Vas Dias (Box 30)
      - Vic Walker (Box 30)
      - Roger Weingarten (Box 30)
      - Bill Wertheim (Box 30)
      - Ruth Whitman (Box 30)
      - Virginia Brady Young (Box 30)
      - Marilyn Zuckerman (Box 30)
      - Dorothea Fox (Box 30)
      - Dicks Gallup (Box 30)
      - Thom Gunn (Box 30)
      - Leonard Halpin (Box 30)
      - Michael Harlan-Rowe (Box 30)
      - James Humphrey (Box 30)
      - Donald Junkins (Box 30)
      - Al Levine (Box 30)
      - Saul Maloff (Box 30)
      - Ron Padgett (Box 30)
      - David Rosenberg (Box 30)
      - David Shapiro (Box 30)
      - Carol Samatowic (Box 30)
      - Ross Palarico (Box 30)
      - Peter Ackroyd (Box 31)
      - Jack Anderson (Box 31)
      - Harry Barba (Box 31)
      - George Cain (Box 31)
      - Halsey Davis (Box 31)
      - William V. Davis (Box 31)
      - Willis Eberman (Box 31)
      - Larry Freifeld (Box 31)
      - William Gilson (Box 31)
      - Gerald Hausman (Box 31)
      - Elaine Gottlieb Hemley (Box 31)
      - Anselm Hallo (Box 31)
      - Michael Horovitz (Box 31)
      - Laurie Janes (Box 31)
      - Emmitt Jarrett (Box 31)
      - Bill Knott (Box 31)
      - James Kaller (Box 31)
      - Lydia Kowalski (Box 31)
      - Charles Levendosky (Box 31)
      - Richard Lewis (Box 31)
      - Roy Lisker (Box 31)
      - Marilyn Lowen (Box 31)
      - Freya Manfred (Box 31)
      - Julio Maryan (Box 31)
      - Adrian Mitchell (Box 31)
      - Haral George Norse (Box 31)
      - John Perlman (Box 31)
      - Kathryn A. Plowitz (Box 31)
      - Rochelle Ratner (Box 31)
      - T.J. Reddy (Box 31)
      - Meir Z. Ribalow (Box 31)
      - William Pitt Root (Box 31)
      - Ruth Lisa Schechter (Box 31)
      - Susan Sherman (Box 31)
      - Elizabeth Singer (Box 31)
      - Lucy Summers (Box 31)
      - Carl Thayler (Box 31)
      - James Thompson (Box 31)
      - Kathy Ungerer (Box 31)
      - Ed Van Zandt (Box 31)
      - Diane Wakoski (Box 31)
      - Meredith Sue Willis (Box 31)
      - Ruby Zagoren (Box 31)
      - Doug Anderson (Box 31)
      - John Beecher (Box 31)
      - Harold Bond (Box 31)
      - Grace Butcher (Box 31)
      - Constance Carrier (Box 31)
      - Robert Hahn (Box 31)
      - Water Jones (Box 31)
      - Barbara Holland (Box 31)
      - Norman Jordan (Box 31)
      - Marc Kaminsky (Box 31)
      - Carolyn Kizer (Box 31)
      - Richard Kostelanutz (Box 31)
      - Cornel Lengyel (Box 31)
      - Carol Lapate (Box 31)
      - Dr. Gloria C. Oden - Poetry (Box 31)
      - Norman Pritchard (Box 31)
      - Alison Raphael (Box 31)
      - Robert Siegel (Box 31)
      - John Swan (Box 31)
      - Ed Zogorski (Box 31)
    - Arts administration (Box 31)
      - Annabelle Simon Cahn (Box 31)
      - Phyliss Gelineau, S.C.S.C., integt. Arts course (Box 31)
      - Rita Cohen, retired principal (Box 31)
      - Keith Cunningham (Box 31)
      - Peter Kleinbard, administrator (Box 31)
      - Jane Favuzza Pick (Box 31)
      - Ruth Shaw (Box 31)
      - Art Administration Applicants (Box 31)
      - Andres Acosta, Vis. Artist (Box 31)
      - U.Conn. Afro-American History Week, 1977 February (Box 31)
    - Visual arts (Box 31)
      - Hernando Asosa, Vis. Artist & music (Box 31)
      - Arthur Miles (Box 31)
      - Feminist Artists - WEB Network (Box 31)
      - Kwame Botwe Asamoah (Box 31)
      - Black Workshop, Inc., New Haven (Box 31)
      - Day of Sharing - Showcase Blk/Hisp Art, 1976 November 12 (Box 31)
      - T.J. Gelting (Box 31)
      - Maurice Libson, Architect (Box 31)
      - David Rejeski (Environ. Des.) (Box 31)
      - Jefferson B. Riley, environm. Architect (Box 31)
    - Dance (Box 31)
      - Ajde Folk Ensemble (Box 31)
      - Diane Adler (Box 31)
      - Donna Blank (Box 31)
      - Bowen Peters Dancers (Box 31)
      - Robin R. Baker (Box 31)
      - Alayne Burger (Box 31)
      - Linda Call (Box 31)
      - Verena Chase (Box 31)
      - Priscilla Colbille (Box 31)
      - Conn. Ballet, Inc. (Box 31)
      - Eric Cooper (Box 31)
      - Sharon Dante (Box 31)
      - Barbara Davis (Box 31)
      - Country Dance, Coun. Folk Music/Dance (Box 31)
      - Barbara Dickinson (Box 31)
      - Frances Kay Doost (Box 31)
      - Emanuel Duodo (Box 31)
      - Judy Dworin (Box 31)
      - Jodi Fabso - Conetic Dance Theatre (Box 31)
      - Lorna Vallone (Box 31)
      - Larry Farrell (Box 31)
      - Sr. Kieran Foley (Box 31)
      - Renee Ganassi (Box 31)
      - Patsy Geyer (Box 31)
      - David Gillette (Box 31)
      - Andrea Hancock/ Dance Movement (Box 31)
      - Lura Hirch/ Dance Movement (Box 31)
      - Mildred Hill (Box 31)
      - Ballet Hispanico/ New York (Box 31)
      - Risa Jaroslow (Box 31)
      - Judith S. Kay (Box 31)
      - June Kennedy (Box 31)
      - Bruce King (Box 31)
      - Joanne Koob (Box 31)
      - Claire Leary (Box 31)
      - Barbara Loeb (Box 31)
      - Jeanne Loeb (Box 31)
      - Lorgo Players L.T.D. (Box 31)
      - Laura Lou Lowry (Box 31)
      - Carol Manago Dance (Box 31)
      - Janet Mariani (Box 31)
      - Alice Martin, Gitlow, Kinsella, CCSC (Box 31)
      - Suzanne Morants (Box 31)
      - Douglas Mitchell (Box 31)
      - Robin Morgan (Box 31)
      - Judy Arbitman Murray, Sculp. Movement (Box 31)
      - Donna O’Sullivan (Box 31)
      - John Perpener (Box 31)
      - Jane Phelan (Box 31)
      - Cathleen Powers (Box 31)
      - Eleo Pomare Dance Co. (Box 31)
      - Barbara Richards Dance Movement (Box 31)
      - Migdalia Rodriguez (Box 31)
      - Robin Rogers (Box 31)
      - Phyllis Rose Dance Co. (Box 31)
      - Sujata Sarathy (Box 31)
      - Susan Sandel (Box 31)
      - Beverly M. Sloatman (Box 31)
      - Katie Sakol (Box 31)
      - Fay Smalen (Box 31)
      - Edith Stephen (Box 31)
      - Joan Stone (Box 31)
      - Agnes Taylor (Box 31)
      - Julio Torres (Box 31)
      - Dick Tracy/ Helen Tracy Folk Dance (Box 31)
      - Creative Movement & Dramatics, Carol White (Box 31)
    - Film, photography and video (Box 31)
      - James Alexander (Box 31)
      - Karen Back, filmmaker (Box 31)
      - Noreen Barney, Video (Box 31)
      - Claude Beller (Box 31)
      - Bonnie Billingham (Box 31)
      - Black, Charles & Eloise, filmmakers, NYC (Box 31)
      - Marleene Booth (Box 31)
      - Linda A. Bourret, Photography (Box 31)
      - Richard Brown, video (Box 31)
      - John Cardoza, video (Box 31)
      - Bob Carignan, photographer (Box 31)
      - Joe Chiara (Box 31)
      - Christine T. Choy (Box 31)
      - Norm Cahn (Box 31)
      - Peter Crawford (Box 31)
      - Don Cyr, photographer (Box 31)
      - Avi Davis-Joan Schwartz, video (Box 31)
      - Anthony Denonno (Box 31)
      - Tony Donovan (Box 31)
    - Music (Box 32)
      - Sherron Adrian (Box 32)
      - Advent - jazz band - New Haven (Box 32)
      - Abraham Adzenyah (Box 32)
      - Kathleen Arecchi (Box 32)
      - Ani Apelian (Box 32)
      - Judy Arel-Orff Music Specialist (Box 32)
      - Music - Ed Askew (Box 32)
      - Dave Barnett - music (Box 32)
      - Robert Benford / Robert Chappell (Box 32)
      - Phillip Charles Bowler (Box 32)
      - Harryson E. Buster - music (Box 32)
      - Michael (thako) Carvin (Box 32)
      - “Casey” twin guitar performers (Box 32)
      - Jeanne Celli - Underneath the grenewud tree (Box 32)
      - Joe Celli (Box 32)
      - Pauline Chaplin (Box 32)
      - Children International (Box 32)
      - Dallas Cline (Box 32)
      - Andy Cohen (Box 32)
      - Connecticut Chamber Music (Box 32)
      - National Chorale NYC (Box 32)
      - Coster, Welling Walach (Box 32)
      - Arthur Custer (Box 32)
      - Sal D’Allessandro (Box 32)
      - David Darling (Box 32)
      - Derdeyn Jazz Group (Box 32)
      - Robert Dick, musician (Box 32)
      - James L. Bino (Box 32)
      - Freeeman Donker (Box 32)
      - Jim Douglas (Box 32)
      - Eastern Brass Quintet (Box 32)
      - Ellington Fellowship Program, Yale (Box 32)
      - Charles Fidlar (Box 32)
      - Jeff Fuller (Box 32)
      - Peter Garnick (Box 32)
      - William Gault (Box 32)
      - Barbara Grissinger (Box 32)
      - Frederick E. Germani (Box 32)
      - Ron Goldman, electronic music (Box 32)
      - Richard Green, Eastern Brass Quinter (Box 32)
      - Robert Gregson (Box 32)
      - Reese E. Griffin, Jr. (Box 32)
      - Friffin and Mariano, explanatory music (Box 32)
      - Larry Groce (Box 32)
      - Joanna Hauser (Box 32)
      - Charlene Garris (Box 32)
      - Michael Jackson, music (Box 32)
      - Virginia Horrigan (Box 32)
      - Janice Carole Jarrett (Box 32)
      - Steven H. Kastuck (Box 32)
      - Skip Keels (Box 32)
      - Rhonda and Rabin Kincaied (Box 32)
      - Jonathan Kramer (Box 32)
      - Folk Music, Bob Levine / Jeff Noonan (Box 32)
      - Tony and Elizabeth Lopez, local music (Box 32)
      - Stephens Evans music (Box 32)
      - Stephen Fectot, songwriter (Box 32)
      - Bill Ferns, music (Box 32)
      - Betty Lytle, folk music (Box 32)
      - Pat Margolin (Box 32)
      - Jim McConaughy (Box 32)
      - Deborah McClothy (Box 32)
      - Charles McPherson (Box 32)
      - Bucky Milam (Box 32)
      - Stephen M. Morris (Box 32)
      - Music - “National Chorale” (Box 32)
      - Robert Maughton (Box 32)
      - Philip Newland (Box 32)
      - Judy Nygren (Box 32)
      - Chick Oakes (Box 32)
      - Yoseph Oxenhandler - music (Box 32)
      - Carolyn and Sandy Paton (Box 32)
      - Performing Groups, music (Box 32)
      - Samuel Quigley (Box 32)
      - Diane Reed (Box 32)
      - Renaissance, consort music (Box 32)
      - John Riley Wells String Quartet (Box 32)
      - Jean and Lee Schilling (Box 32)
      - Tom Schmutzler, music historical (Box 32)
      - David Sermershine, music comp. (Box 32)
      - Billy Skinner, music (Box 32)
      - Bruce Smith (Box 32)
      - Leo Smith (Box 32)
      - Liz Smith (Box 32)
      - Christine Snyder, Music/ horn/woodwind quintet (Box 32)
      - Elizabeth I. Snyder (Box 32)
      - Jeanne and Phil Staniszewski (Box 32)
      - Neil Stratton, music (Box 32)
      - Pam Swing (Box 32)
      - Carolyn Tewari, Laxmi Ganesh Tewari (Box 32)
      - Gary Towlen (Box 32)
      - Paul Tracy, music Africa (Box 32)
      - Howard Tunelle (Box 32)
      - Leland Wade, music (Box 32)
      - Jeff Warner (Box 32)
      - Frank Warner (Box 32)
      - Arthur Welwood, CCSC (Box 32)
      - Billy Williams (Box 32)
      - Young Audiences, NYC (Box 32)
      - John Ziegenhagen (Box 32)
      - Susan Zimmerman (Box 32)
      - Phil Zimmerman, music group (Last Fair Deal) (Box 32)
    - Film (Box 32)
      - Nick Doab (Box 32)
      - Gary Drucker (Box 32)
      - Cornel Ferat (Box 32)
      - Cynthia Freitag, filmmaker (Box 32)
      - Juan Fuentes (Box 32)
      - Fred Gordon (Box 32)
      - Robert Gilson (Box 32)
      - Shalom Gorewitz (Box 32)
      - Raumond L. Greenfield, film (Box 32)
      - Bruce Grund (Box 32)
      - Inghect Fruttner, photographer (Box 32)
      - Bob Gumpper, photo- lithography (Box 32)
      - Michael Harder, filmmaking (Box 32)
      - John Harris (Box 32)
      - Richard Hubbard, photography (Box 32)
      - Joyce Jabbour (Box 32)
      - Walton Jones (Box 32)
      - Roy Lisky, video (Box 32)
      - Phillip Lebowitz, film video (Box 32)
      - Brian Levis, filmmaking (Box 32)
      - Robert Levi (Box 32)
      - Jayne Kantor (Box 32)
      - Maryland Lincoln, photographer (Box 32)
      - Lawrence Loewinger (Box 32)
      - Gerry Lombardi, video (Box 32)
      - Judith Mann (Box 32)
      - Sally Meiss, photographer (Box 32)
      - Me Two Production, film, Joan Walden, Julia Gibson (Box 32)
      - Gayle Miller, photography (Box 32)
      - John Moore (Box 32)
      - Sandra Moore (Box 32)
      - Douglas Nichols (Box 32)
      - Sharry Nunan, video (Box 32)
      - Darit Ofer, filmmaker, NYC (Box 32)
      - Susan Opotow (Box 32)
      - Guido Organschi, photographer (Box 32)
      - Don Peccerilo, video (Box 32)
      - Thomas Perkins, photography (Box 32)
      - Richard Place (Box 32)
      - Andy Plesser (Box 32)
      - Vicki Polon (Box 32)
      - Elliot Porter - Norm Cohn (Box 32)
      - Charles Reich (Box 32)
      - Geno Rodriguez (Box 32)
      - Angel Luis Roman (Box 32)
      - Ruth Rocko, filmmaker - video (Box 32)
      - Garrett Schenck (Box 32)
      - Thomas Spence (Box 32)
      - Jidith Stauffer, photography (Box 32)
      - Victor Sullivan, filmmaking (Box 32)
      - Aldo Tanhellini (Box 32)
      - Leslie Ann Valgard Thornton, film (Box 32)
      - Walter Ungerer (Box 32)
      - John Basey, filmmaker (Box 32)
      - Shawn Watson - James Baker Hall, owners of Marrix (Box 32)
      - Joan Walden (Box 32)
      - Pat Wlker, video (Box 32)
      - Jane Weiner (Box 32)
      - Elizabeth Winer (Box 32)
      - Weston Woods Studios (Box 32)
      - Katy Weisser, photographer (Box 32)
      - Meridith Sue Willis, Video (Box 32)
      - Robert Yeomano (Box 32)
      - George Zabriskie (Box 32)
      - Leonard Zapala (Box 32)
  - School Files (Box 33)
    - New Haven - V.A.P. Evaluation Materials, 1973-1974 (Box 33)
    - New Haven Schools, 1974-1975 (Box 33)
    - New Haven Public Schools, 1973-1974 (Box 33)
    - New Haven Schools, 1971-1973 (Box 33)
    - New Haven Catherine Brennan School (Box 33)
    - New Haven Creative Arts Workshop (Box 33)
    - New Haven Fact - Black Artists (Box 33)
    - New Haven Helene Grant School (Box 33)
    - New Haven Morning Sun Free School (Box 33)
    - New Haven Yale University Afro-American Cultural center (Box 33)
    - New Haven Public Schools, 1976-1977 (Box 33)
    - New Haven Lee High School (Box 33)
    - New Haven Lee High School Annex (Box 33)
    - New Haven Sacred Heart Elementary School (Box 33)
    - New Haven So. Central Community College (Box 33)
    - New Haven Troup Middle School (Box 33)
    - New Haven Truman School (Box 33)
    - New Haven University of New Haven World Music Project (Box 33)
    - New Haven Edgewood School (Box 33)
    - New Haven Winchester Elementary School (Box 33)
    - New Haven Martin Luther King School (Box 33)
    - New Haven Worthington Hooker School (Box 33)
    - New Haven Lincoln- Bassett School (Box 33)
    - New Haven Hillhouse High School (Box 33)
    - New Haven Hillhouse and Lee High School, A.I.S., 1975-1976 (Box 33)
    - New Haven High School in the Community (Box 33)
    - New Haven Beecher School (Box 33)
    - New Haven Polly T. McCabe Center (Box 33)
    - New Haven Mary Boyle, New Haven Arts Project (Box 33)
    - New Haven Southern Connecticut State College (Betty Hahn) (Box 33)
    - New Haven Southern Connecticut State College (Phyllis Gelineau) (Box 33)
    - New Haven Music Education (Box 33)
    - New Haven City Spirit, Grant Program, 1977-1978 (Box 33)
    - New Haven Arts in Education Public Schools and Arts Council (Box 33)
    - Newington - Children’s Hospital, 1974-1975 (Box 33)
    - Newington - Children’s Hospital, 1974-1975 (Box 33)
    - Newington - Children’s Hospital, the Fun Place to Go (Box 33)
    - Newington School System (Box 33)
    - Newington Southeast School (Box 33)
    - New London - New Independent High School (Box 33)
    - New London - Nuestra Casa (Box 33)
    - New London - The Williams School (Box 33)
    - New London - High School (Box 33)
    - New London - Nathan Hale School (Box 33)
    - New London - Edgerton School (Box 33)
    - New Milford High School (Box 33)
    - Newtown High School (Box 33)
    - Newtown Lumia (Box 33)
    - Niantic - Creative Playschool, Inc. (Box 33)
    - North Haven - Montowese School (Box 33)
    - North Haven - Ben Haven (Box 33)
    - North Haven - High School (Box 33)
    - Norwalk - Community College, 1975-1976 (Box 33)
    - Norwalk - School System (Box 33)
    - Norwich - Buckingham School (Box 33)
    - Norwalk - McMahon High School (Box 33)
    - Norwalk - Honey Hill School (Box 33)
    - Norwalk - the New School (Piaget-based) (Box 33)
    - Old Saybrook High School (Box 33)
    - Portland Board of Education, 1976-1977 (Box 33)
    - Pomfret Community School (Box 33)
    - Prospect Schools (Box 33)
    - Putnam High School (Box 33)
    - West Redding - John Read Middle School, 1974-1975 (Box 33)
    - West Redding - Joel Barlow High School (Box 33)
    - Redding Elementary School (Box 33)
    - Ridgefield High School, 1974-1975 (Box 33)
    - Ridgefield Public Schools (Box 33)
    - Ridgefield High School (Box 33)
    - Scotland Elementary School (Box 33)
    - Riverside - Dundee School (Box 33)
    - Avon High School, 1976-1977 (Box 34)
    - Barkhamsted Elementary School (Box 34)
    - Avon Cultural Committee (Box 34)
    - Berlin High School (Box 34)
    - C.M. McGee School, Berlin (Box 34)
    - Bethany Community Elementary School (Box 34)
    - Bethany Community Elementary School (Box 34)
    - Bethel Middle School (Box 34)
    - Bloomfield Board of Education, 1973-1975 (Box 34)
    - Bloomfield Arts Council (Box 34)
    - Bloomfield Public Schools, 1975-1976 (Box 34)
    - Bloomfield - Wintonbury School (Box 34)
    - Bloomfield - Middle School (Box 34)
    - Bloomfield - Laurel School (Box 34)
    - Bloomfield - Metacomet School (Box 34)
    - Bloomfield - Wintonbury School (Box 34)
    - Bloomfield High School (Box 34)
    - Bloomfield Jr. High School (Box 34)
    - Bloomfield Vincent School (Box 34)
    - Bloomfield Sacred Heart School, 1976-1977 (Box 34)
    - Bloomfield Sacred Heart School, 1973-1976 (Box 34)
    - Branford P.T.A. (Box 34)
    - Branford Wightwood School (Box 34)
    - Branford Intermediate School (Box 34)
    - Burr School - Higganum (Box 34)
    - Branford Middle School (Box 34)
    - Bridgeport Public Library (Burroughs Library) (Box 34)
    - Bridgeport Public Schools (Box 34)
    - Bridgeport Hall School (Box 34)
    - Bridgeport Wheeler School (Box 34)
    - Bridgeport Park City Alternative High School (Box 34)
    - Bridgeport Whittier School (Box 34)
    - Bridgeport ABCD - Ben Johnson (Box 34)
    - Bridgeport Catholic Family Services (Box 34)
    - Bridgeport Central High School (Box 34)
    - Bridgeport Longfellow School (Box 34)
    - Bridgeport Arts High School (Box 34)
    - Bridgeport R.E.S.C.U.E. (Box 34)
    - Bristol - Visiting Artists Program, 1975-1976 (Box 34)
    - Bristol - Board of Education (Box 34)
    - Bristol - Westwood School (Box 34)
    - Bristol - Schools (Box 34)
    - Bristol - Evaluation: Westwood Elementary, 1974-1975 (Box 34)
    - Bristol - Bingham School (Box 34)
    - Bristol - Hubbell School (Box 34)
    - Bristol - Mountain View School (Box 34)
    - Bristol - Patterson School (Box 34)
    - Brooklyn - Brooklyn School (Box 34)
    - Burlington - Mills High School (Box 34)
    - Canton - Creative Arts Council (Box 34)
    - Cheshire High School (Box 34)
    - Cheshire Highland Elementary School (Box 34)
    - Colebrook - Colebrook School (Box 34)
    - Cos Cob - Cos Cob School (Box 34)
    - Danbury - Women’s Political Caucus (Box 34)
    - Danbury - Art Show and Sale (Box 34)
    - Danbury - Stradley Rough School (Box 34)
    - Danbury - Morris Street Elementary School (Box 34)
    - Bristol - Memorial Blvd. Jr. High School (Box 34)
    - Plainfield - Quinebaug Valley Community College (Box 34)
    - Danielson (Box 34)
    - Darien - Cherry Lawn School (Box 34)
    - Middlesex Jr. High School, Darien (Box 34)
    - Derby - Stand, Inc. (Box 34)
    - Memorial Patons - Pictures (Box 34)
    - East Hampton - Memorial School (Box 34)
    - East Hampton - Center School (Box 34)
    - East Hampton - O’Connell School (Box 34)
    - East Hampton - High School (Box 34)
    - East Hampton - Silver Lane School (Box 34)
    - East Lyme - Flanders School (Box 34)
    - Resumes from artists - out of state V.A.P. Program (Box 34)
  - A.I.S. by Art Form (Box 35)
    - Poetry and Writing (Box 35)
      - Lonnie Black (Box 35)
      - Bill E. Basquecte (Box 35)
      - Carol Berge (Box 35)
      - Steve Berman (Box 35)
      - Lonnie Black - 2 (Box 35)
      - John Beckman (Box 35)
      - Raymond Biasotti (Box 35)
      - Gigi Bradford Cole (Box 35)
      - Ray Bremser (Box 35)
      - Lynn H. Bumbray - Poetry (Box 35)
      - Helen Carlson (Box 35)
      - Lonnie Carter (Box 35)
      - Karen Chase (Box 35)
      - James Coleman (Box 35)
      - Elsa Colligan (Box 35)
      - Alan De Larm (Box 35)
      - Alexis DeVeaux (Box 35)
      - Sharleen Dickinson (Box 35)
      - Jo Disco (Box 35)
      - David Eliet (Box 35)
      - Elizabeth H. Egloff (Box 35)
      - Poet - John Engeman (Box 35)
      - Theodore Enslin - Poetry (Box 35)
      - Hal Eskesen (Box 35)
      - Jose- Angel Figueroa - Poetry (Box 35)
      - Roger Gaiess (Box 35)
      - Brendan Galvin (Box 35)
      - Peggy Garrison (Box 35)
      - Richard Jeller (Box 35)
      - Robert P. Girard (Box 35)
      - Dolores Greene (Box 35)
      - Verta Mae Grosvenor (Box 35)
      - Larry Halfkenney (Box 35)
      - Mark Holliday (Box 35)
      - Susan Harris (Box 35)
      - Alan Hutchinson (Box 35)
      - David Jackson (Box 35)
      - Writer: Mae Jackson (Box 35)
      - Poetry: Laurie James (Box 35)
      - Erica Jong (Box 35)
      - William Joyce (Box 35)
      - Melinda Kahn (Box 35)
      - Tony LaPenta (Box 35)
      - Helen Lawson (Box 35)
      - Todd S. J. Lawson (Box 35)
      - Richard Lees (Box 35)
      - Playwright - Werner Liepalt (Box 35)
      - Lyn Lipman Lifshin (Box 35)
      - William Logan - poetry (Box 35)
      - Kathy London Cr. Writing Teacher (Box 35)
      - John Love (Box 35)
      - Clarence Major (Box 35)
      - Poetry - Fay Manus (Box 35)
      - Wendy Mark (Box 35)
      - Barry Marshall (Box 35)
      - Sharon Martin - Playwright (Box 35)
      - Kathleen Meagher (Box 35)
      - Raymond Metrulis (Box 35)
      - Mary Ellen Mininberg (Box 35)
      - Judith Minty (Box 35)
      - Honor Moore - NR (Box 35)
      - Poetry - Glenn Morazzini (Box 35)
      - Steven A. Otfinoski - Poetry (Box 35)
      - Phil Paradis (Box 35)
      - John Perlman (Box 35)
      - Richard Plaetz (Box 35)
      - Charles Plynell (Box 35)
      - Lawrence Rapoport - Poetry (Box 35)
      - Mark Rudman - NR (Box 35)
      - Will Schmitz (Box 35)
      - Virginia Scott (Box 35)
      - Hugh Seidman (Box 35)
      - Gene Seymour (Box 35)
      - Poetry - Bonnie Shapiro (Box 35)
      - Jacqueline Shelton (Box 35)
      - William Jay Smith (Box 35)
      - Rodney Steier (Box 35)
      - Martha Stearns - Poet (Box 35)
      - Terry Stokes - NR (Box 35)
      - Jody Swilky (Box 35)
      - George Sylvester (Box 35)
      - Helen Tartat (Box 35)
      - Alexander Taylor (Box 35)
      - Adrienne Walfert (Box 35)
      - Lynn Tritton (Box 35)
      - Stephen Thomas (Box 35)
      - Steve Yaffe, Playwright - NH (Box 35)
      - Kip Zegus (Box 35)
      - Jonas Zdanys (Box 35)
      - Marilyn Zuckerman - NR (Box 35)
      - Poets-in-the-Schools Brochure Material )out of state) (Box 35)
- Series 6. Educational Records, 1967-1976
  - Education Program, General, 1966 - 1975 (Box 36)
    - School Intake Info Questionnaire (Box 36)
    - Education Planning, 1975-1976 (Box 36)
    - Education Staff Meeting, 1973-1974 (Box 36)
    - Visual Artists in Residence, NEA grant, 1970-1973 (Box 36)
    - Artist-in Schools Guidelines, 1972-1973 (Box 36)
    - Richard Place memo, Program History, 1972-1973 (Box 36)
    - Richard Place Field Report, 1971-1973 (Box 36)
    - Whittier School, V.A.P., 1971-1972 (Box 36)
    - V.A.P. Brochure, Mailing list, 1972-1973 (Box 36)
    - V.A.P. Conference, R.E.S.C.U.E., 1972, May (Box 36)
    - Special Project Forms, 1972-1973 (Box 36)
    - A.I.R. film proposal, 1972-1973 (Box 36)
    - V.A.P. Support letters, Spring, 1973 (Box 36)